

RAHMAT FAUZIN PRASETYO

Kendal, Central Java, 51318 | 085727796168 | rahmatfauzanprasetyoofficial@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/rahmat-

fauzin-prasetyo-51729b1a5/

Profile

Hello, My name is Rahmat Fauzin Prasetyo as recently graduated of Civil Engineering at Sebelas Maret University and i am currently studying D4 Civil Engineering at Sepuluh Nopember Technology Institute. I am a person who is active, thorough and detailed in doing every job. I have passion on Civil Engineering and proficient in using Microsoft Office, AutoCAD, SketchUp, SAP 2000, Autodesk Revit, Tekla and i am reasonably proficient in both written and spoken English. I am able to work under pressure, work with a team, ready to be moved out of my town, and like toexplore new things such experience to learn.

Skills

- Microsoft Office
- SketchUp
- AutoCAD

- Autodesk Revit
- Tekla
- Good Observation

Work Experience

PT. Intinusa Cipta Persada (Sukoharjo, Central Java)

Project Estimator (August 2021 – August 2022)

In PT Intinusa Cipta Persada as a Project Estimator and having a job description can make BoQ, estimate unit price analysis for structural (civil) building work, architecture, infrastructure, and concretr construction. Achievement: Obtained various project agreements in 1 year

PT. PP (Persero) (Sleman, Yogyakarta)

Internship Student (August 2020 - Oktober 2020)

In PT PP (Persero) as an Internship Student at project implementation division and have a job description carrying out work in the field or project location, to ensure that the work meets the established quality standards.

Education

Sebelas Maret University (Surakarta, Indonesia)

Diploma 3 Civil Engineering – GPA 3.56

Sepuluh Nopember Technology Institute (Surabaya, Indonesia)

Diploma 4 Civil Engineering

Organizational Experience

Chief Executive of Promotions and Publications at Sebelas Maret University in Kendal 2019-2020

Certficates

- 1. Sertifikat Kompetensi Ahli Teknik Bangunan Gedung (March 2021 March 2024)
- 2. Listening and Reading Official Institutional Score Report (ETS TOEIC 470)
- 3. Sertifikat Praktik Kerja Lapangan PT PP (Persero)
 Construction Project in Gadjah Mada University APSLC, DILC, TILC, and FRC buildings